Hi, in this video, I will show you how to use the new platform at learning.
Let's first open my learning page in the top menu and you will see the list of all your
courses.
And now click on any course you interested.
I will show you how to use them on my own course.
On the right side, you see the navigation panel where you can see all the course sections
and lessons.
You can expand them and to see other lessons.
Also, some lessons may have resources; it can be some documents or links.
You may need to download or open and they will help you to finish some lessons.
At the top of your site, you see the progress bar.
It tells you how many lessons you complete.
And after you complete all the lessons, you can get a certificate.
I will tell you how to get it in the end of this course.
Also you have the video player at the left side and you have some controls.
You can play a pulse video.
You can also forward it to 5 seconds or back.
You can also change the speed of the video to make it faster or slower, but then normally
use 1.25.
It's a comfort speed.
You can also, on the right side, enable captions to see text what outer tells on the video
or you can just off it.
And you can also change the video quality if you need to increase or reduce it.
And what is also used for the full screen, mode and you can also access from it.
Okay, let's go a bit down and you have the Q&A section.
On this page, you can see all the questions students ask on this course and you can also
ask your own question.
You can choose the topic you want to ask, get something about course you need help or
it's your face with some issues and then click continue, provide a title, your question
and publish it.
Make an ability to make some notes for specific lesson.
You just click this icon and it types something and click save.
And on the notes page, you can see all the notes and it's private you on only you can
see it no other students.
So now you know how to use the new platform, do you in the next videos?